Yeah.
Hi, my name is Peter Parker.
You don't remember me, but I have something
to tell you that's gonna sound crazy.
But it's the truth.
And I know you're gonna believe me because
you're very good at telling when I'm lying.
Evie, can you check the
calibration of my targeting matrix?
That doesn't feel zeroed into me.
Checking target calibration.
Hey, Evie, take five.
Standing by.
We used to know each other.
We were together.
But something bad was going to happen.
And the only way to stop it
was to make everyone forget me.
First did and lied to you, let's go.
Oh my gosh, we're here, we made it.
MJ, come on.
Including you.
Pretend like you're not the happy suit
ever been in your entire life right now.
Thank you.
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
And sometimes Spider-Man
has to do the hard
thing even if it breaks
Peter Parker's heart.
and maybe that's my responsibility
to live alone with the truth.
But the truth is MJ that I love you.
And I hope that deep down something inside
of you remembers that you love me too.
Suspect is 5, 8, 5, 10, medium build.
But until then, I'm just
gonna be Spider-Man.
Members of the Man Freddy crime syndicate
were apprehended by Spider-Man yesterday.
Hey, we live on the same floor.
Does anybody ever come up here?
I don't let's say like a specialist.
We've just been using it for storage.
It's perfect.
Hey everyone, sophomore
year and that is back.
Older, wiser, flyer.
Let's go.
Whoa.
What is on your face?
How do you feel about it?
I mean, you look like an assistant coach.
Hey, you sure you want to do this scorpion?
Did you miss Miss Spidey?
If I drop you from here how long you
think it would take you to hit the ground?
Well, I don't know.
You tell me.
Let's send this on a high note, huh?
Yo, line me.
What happened?
The wolf!
All the evidence you get in
need is in the trunk of his car.
You trying to take my job, Spider-Man?
Hey, you guys are the professionals.
I'm just the volunteer.
It's a new New York.
Thanks to Spider-Man, crime
rates have dropped to a record load.
Police and damage control give
much of the credit to the master hero.
Initiate HUD test.
Armed robbery at Civic Union Bank.
In the past six months, he has
taken down every major crime war to
cross the fly burrows, including the
super powered ninja group the hand.
He is the pride of New York City.
The hero every grown-up relies
on, and every kid wants to be.
Final semester, MIT.
Oh, my gosh.
We're graduating in a month.
We've made so many memories.
Where do I begin?
Night-swimming in the Charles
River with Jim and Wiley.
The infamous food find at
the Banana Lounge, pulling
all-nighters and stud-5
with MJ and Nate Dow.
It feels like yesterday I was
sitting on a roof with MJ dreaming
about coming here together
and I still can't believe we did it.
I'm so grateful for all
the friends that I've made.
I couldn't imagine going
through this with anyone else.
Dad, who do you think
is actually watching this?
I don't know, but maybe someone.
Okay, bye someone.
Bye, we're done.
No!
I mean, we're talking about
downtown Brooklyn and broad daylight.
High profile, job like that.
You know the fossil was involved.
Yeah.
I hear you, but can you prove it?
Yeah, I'm going through his financial records
and I'm following his crew every night.
Do you do anything besides work?
You know the saying, you
do something he loved me.
You don't work a day in your life.
Came in about it.
Mom, it was my calculator.
Trust me, I, being married
to the job never ends well.
Don't worry about it.
I'll be OK. Oh, yeah.
You still getting them headaches, though?
Yeah, but um, but I'll be fine.
I don't know, man.
I think your body's trying
to tell you something.
Like, you need to get out of
that suit every once in a while.
Mom, do you know where my calculator is?
I don't know about that.
What you need is some
real human connection.
Oh, what?
And we're not connecting?
Nah, dude.
I don't know your name, your
face, or nothing about you.
I don't think you've asked
me a question about my life.
I'm sure I have.
Yeah, what are my kids names?
Well, for starters, your
son's name's Poppy.
Is it Spider-Man?
I can't tell you this, we are.
That means it's Spider-Man?
Oh, gosh.
A hijack tank is heading
southbound past 34th Street.
All available units respond.
Hey, you getting this?
More work.
Look at you.
Look at us here out there.
I'm so sorry.
I gotta go.
Whoa!
I got you, Spidey!
No, no, I don't need you.
Hey, I dropped!
You OK, kid?
Yeah, you're OK. See you later.
You wouldn't know it just
by looking at it, but this very
streak was completely destroyed
in the battle of New York.
No!
Come back, come on!
What the hell, Frank?
You just hit me in the van.
Quit your win, Frank.
We're not doing that again, Frank.
You got them right, would not.
It's time you're going to
get the hell out of my way.
Well, you mean instead of saving your life?
Yeah.
You're going to talk about
that Staten Island bullshit again.
Marvel, you said it not me.
Look, man, you can't just shoot
yourself out of every situation.
And innocent people get hurt.
What do you think's that
range of that tank, dumb, dumb?
Shoot yourself.
I guess.
This frickin' guy.
Mother.
Go home, Frank!
I'm not kill this kid.
The wolf, you're going
to stop that thing or what?
He's heading straight for the
damage control detention center.
I'm trying.
Try harder.
There's a lot of scary
dudes like up in there.
Who do you think put them in there?
Let's go, Scorpion.
Moving day.
All right, everybody clear out this
guy is orphaned and dangerous.
Get out of the vehicle, ma'am.
I was thinking the same thing.
Spiderman?
Where am I?
What the?
Keep her for questioning.
Clear the building.
Enjoy the ride, Scorpion.
You won't be seeing
my staylight in Supermax.
Scorpions are not journal, buddy.
Get the prisoner out of here now!
You gotta take us now!
The building is in reach!
Go!
Change of plans!
Take it to the Alabama Bellevue!
What?
That's an order from the rectum rescue.
Go!
Now!
Copy that!
Hey!
What?
How did I get up here?
Uh... Spider-Man!
Save me, would you?
Who are you?
You can see me.
Tell me who you are.
You first.
Hey.
You pushed me out.
Interesting.
What the hell was that?
Did you just try to jump in on my mind?
You know, the whole time
you've been chasing me, you
forgot to ask yourself a
very important question.
What's in the tank?
Spiderman?
What just happened?
I don't know.
Hey, good job.
You guys okay?
You good?
I swear.
All the things I said I did.
I don't remember doing anything.
It's okay.
Look, let these people
take good care of you.
I would never hurt you.
Okay.
I love you swear to her.
Yeah.
All right, buddy.
All right.
Hey, what do you got here?
Get this chopper took
scorpion to Bellevue 10 minutes
later, and guard walked
him right out the door.
What?
Mm-hmm.
What about the tank?
Stolen from the damage
control warehouse in Brooklyn.
Driver was a janitor of a work there.
You got a motive?
Nada.
And no criminal record, Scorpion
must have gotten to her somehow.
Yeah, maybe.
What do you mean, maybe?
I mean, I don't know.
But I know someone to mine.
What are you going?
You keep following the leads on Scorpion.
I'm gonna go talk to someone.
Hi.
Uh, is this 3250 bargain beach?
Five ions, yes.
Okay.
All right, you think I
know what that means?
Take up your clothes.
Uh, what?
You don't want clothes in the manual.
Ditch the leotard.
This is not a leotard.
Your tech said that this was your office.
This is my office.
Get in.
I'm fine, thanks.
My office, my rules.
This way, you get to
enjoy a nice relaxing soak.
And I get to see that you
don't have any weapons.
And we both win.
OK.
Really?
Would you never take that off?
No, you know, it defeats
the whole anomalous thing.
Even for your girlfriend
or boyfriend or whatever.
There's a lot of conjecture on that.
And super graphic artwork, have you seen
the one with you and the 10 mysterious?
I've seen it.
I'm hard to unsee to be honest,
but look, I don't have anyone.
I just kind of keep to myself.
Oh, by yourself all the time?
I wonder if you're so sad.
Not so sad.
A little bit.
Could we just talk
about what I came here to
talk to you about the
attack on damage control?
Yes.
So that is more your area.
Like small potato stuff.
Whereas the new Avengers
are focusing on big potato stuff.
Right.
Okay.
Well, there's more to it than that.
You know, deal to driver and
the others who were helping.
It was like someone was
talking to me through them.
Like someone was looking
at me through their eyes.
And you're wondering if it's mind control.
Exactly.
Like how they used on me in the red room.
And the other way of those.
Right.
No.
I don't think so.
I actually think it's probably
more like possession.
Possession?
Mm-hmm.
Like a ghost?
Or a demon?
Or a lasha, we have Leshim.
Leshim rules the forest and can possess...
Sorry.
Whatever it is, they're
looking for something.
This is the fourth attack on the
damage control facility this month.
What do you think they're looking for?
I don't know.
But you know what?
After the attack today,
there was a cross
agency cybersecurity
alert that got triggered.
Someone accessed the
damage control restricted servers
using credentials from 13
employees from the waste station.
They all searched for the same thing.
VMAX.
What does that mean?
be alien tech or secreted weapon
programs or launch codes or I don't know
this is for you to figure out this
is small baby potato stuff not okay
You know, you're not
completely anonymous anymore.
I have seen your belly button.
Okay.
Bye.
Hi, I got an appointment with...
Director Metzker.
Yes.
Please step through the scanner.
Enhanced human-detected,
superior strength, superior
agility, heightened senses,
exogenous DNA, arachnid.
Please remove your face
covering for identity scan.
I can't do that.
Failure to remove your face covering
will result in defensive measures.
Defensive measures.
Guys, guys, guys, I can't take my mask off.
I'm Spider-Man.
He's all right.
That is... My apologies.
We are so glad you're here.
Bill Metzka, director of damage control.
How are you?
I'm good, thank you.
We had to beef up security around here,
but I hope we didn't give you a fright.
No, not at all.
All right, come on this way.
This floor is mostly
research of administrative.
Downstairs, we have incident
cleanup, laboratories, agent training.
Oh.
Hey, what are they doing here?
It's OK.
The hand works for us now.
After you brought them in, I
realized that fundamentally
there are a group of
kids without a leader.
All they needed was a little direction.
And suddenly, all the things
that made them dangerous
turned them into an invaluable
part of our security team.
Or may I touch you up?
Or to know how good it is.
You can look at the many threats
that face us and see only danger.
Or you can see opportunity.
Oh, OK.
Wow, look at that.
And the hands of shocker,
these are a nuisance.
But it doesn't mean we can't learn from
the technology or respect the innovation.
Our mission is to redirect destructive
energy into something useful.
That's the true meaning of damage control.
You careful with that.
Right this way?
I wanted to talk to you about
the reason to tax on the agency.
There's been four, right?
Please, have a seat.
You are right.
It appears we're faced with
the threat we can't control.
One we can't even see.
But you can.
That's all the security footage.
I also read Detective DeWolf's report.
I believe you understand
exactly what we're up against.
Someone there was something
that could hop into people's minds.
But not yours.
No.
I mean, it tried, but it couldn't.
I'm going to be honest with you.
Well, not heels right now.
God forbid if we were to get in here
and find whatever it is it's looking for.
The consequences could be unimaginable.
Well, let me guess, is whatever
it's looking for in that giant vault?
There are some things because
of the nature of my job I cannot
tell you, but I believe you
are best defense against this.
You're the only one who can sense it.
You're the only one who's immune to it.
I'm counting on you to defeat it.
That's a pretty good speech, director.
I'll do everything that I can, I promise.
Well, then, consider yourself
a friend of damage control.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
Oh, I wanted to ask.
The phrase VMAX doesn't
mean anything to you.
Does it?
No.
Where'd you hear that?
Oh, it's just, you know,
nature being a superhero.
There are some things
that just can't tell you.
Anyway, I'll see you later.
You guys are doing great.
Keep it up.
I don't think Metzker
knows any more than we do,
but I told him I'd do
whatever I can to help.
Do you want to help?
The best thing you
could do is find Scorpion.
He's our only lead.
Yeah, I know.
I have every camera in the city
running a facial recognition scan floor.
That sounds super illegal, Spider-Man.
I'm gonna pretend I didn't hear that.
Yeah, probably for the best.
But look, if he shows his face, we'll know.
Do you love any?
Any things?
Down on the end.
Thanks.
I'll call you back.
Ah.
Easy.
Hey, uh, also, you got
any sharp fire energy?
Yeah.
Oh, no, no, no.
I don't want any.
That's the full kill you.
All my friends were drinking them
during finals, and now they're addicted.
So I'm going to need
you to not sell me any.
And rise my face.
Please, do not sell
this guy any sharp fire.
Sure.
Whatever.
Actually, I'll take one.
We'll ask the one.
That may be two.
And then never sell me any damage.
Oh my gosh!
Guys, who did you?
Can I have that?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
Oh, see, you've stumbled across my board.
I'm not one of those weirdos.
I swear.
He actually saved me and my
friends lives a few times in high school.
Oh, cool.
Yeah, yeah.
Ever since I've just been
trying to figure out who he is.
Not to unmask him to the world or
anything, just to know, you know?
Hopefully you thank him face-to-face.
I actually created this app.
The monitors are sightings.
What you created is by each writer.
You heard of it.
Nice.
Wait, it's a sweeter man.
Well, chat room right there.
Now, we know he's definitely from Queens.
Not the biggest revelation.
But I have been able to narrow
it down to prime suspects.
Yeah.
If you knew where they were, it
wouldn't really blow your mind.
I'm sure.
That, by the way.
Oh, I'm... Oh, there's like
50 people on our apartment.
It's just basically
speaking at least two of
them are sociopaths,
which is kind of cool.
Nice flowers.
Oh, there are... Housewarming gift.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
Most people just brought beer and chips.
It's very nice.
I'm MJ.
I'm a...
I'm a... I'm a... Mainer.
Uh, Maynard.
Oh, you two don't know each other?
Uh, no, I'm, uh, neighbor.
Friendly neighbor.
Sorry.
So, how was the interview?
I'm gonna go put these in water.
It was nice to meet you, Maynard.
Nerd.
Maynard.
Yeah.
Did you go?
Please tell me that you went.
Yeah, no, I went.
And?
And I got the job.
Oh, my God, I'm due.
That's amazing.
I turned it down.
What?
Yeah, I don't want to work
for some solace corporation.
They're not all solace.
OK, they're all mostly solace.
But don't you want, like, health insurance?
Yeah, of course I do.
But what cost?
It depends on your deductible.
Oh, you mean like your principles?
Yes.
Sorry.
I don't know.
I know it sounds cheesy, but...
Something he's just telling me that I'm
supposed to be waiting for something.
Great, you know.
Okay, um, to, uh, waiting
for something great.
Waiting for something great.
Well, the weight is over.
Oh!
You knew him.
Dude, this is top shelf.
Just like you.
Oh!
I'm gonna hide this.
I'll lift it this whole thing again.
But what if Ned needs the
fire of a thousand sharks?
You need heart palpitations.
You can't save everyone.
I can try.
That's my girl.
I'm sorry.
I got it.
When we get into MIT,
we should lift together.
Yeah, for sure.
Yeah, I love that.
Be a fresh start.
And we'll all be together.
Yeah, now you're right.
Yeah, I'm a fresh start.
You're going to forget who I am.
You can't remember
what you're talking about.
It's OK.
I'm going to come and find
you, and I'll explain everything.
I don't want to wait.
Wait and tell me, maybe send me again.
My name is Peter Parker,
and I... I could call for me.
Is there anything else?
No.
Hey.
They think you don't have to
listen to me and they've got power.
You know, this whole
thing and get really scary.
You know that?
We are.
It's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change very quickly
ways that we can't even imagine right now.
Believe me, I know.
I don't think you do now.
What do you mean?
Oh, good!
I, uh, I live here.
I just don't...
I'm gonna grab my stuff.
Tell me short.
Oh, cute dog.
Oh, shit.
You lie.
Hi, Peter.
You have 107 new alerts.
Please check that clock.
What?
It's so happening.
The results of your body scan show a surge in
the hormones associated with your arachnid DNA,
resulting in the formation of organic web spinorets
and dangerously heightened sensory receptors.
OK, but I feel fine.
For long isolation or emotional trauma
could be contributing to this sudden change.
Have you experienced
any recent traumatic events?
Peter?
I'm fine, Evie.
You don't seem fine.
I recommend you take
some time to rebalance.
Well, that's not really
an option, isn't it?
Mechanical web shooters and organic
webs cannot be used simultaneously.
Nowhere.
Alert.
Census are overloaded.
The lurk, census are overloaded.
Alert, census, census, census are alert.
What the hell was that?
Your heightened senses are taking
in too much information at once.
Okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
All right, organic webs.
Peter, two hat'em.
He was cool.
Oh!
Oh my god, that's hideous.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, that didn't work.
We're gonna go outside.
Come on!
And we'll!
Stop!
What's going on, Evie?
Shots fired at the damage
control data center in Manhattan.
Suspect facial match with Scorpion.
Okay, I'm on my way.
Come on, three, two, one, stop!
No!
I'm sorry.
Where are you going?
I don't know what you're looking for.
I'm looking for B-Max.
I don't know anything.
I'll see for myself.
I'm sorry, I'm late.
I've had a really crazy day.
I have scorpion.
Do we really gotta keep doing this?
My head is killing me.
You think I'm scorpion?
What's happening to you?
You can't sense me anymore.
You.
Warning.
Arachnic hormones increasing.
Who are you?
Do you know who you are?
What the hell?
Somebody get a medic.
The wolf is she hurt?
Is she okay?
No.
Just let me down.
What is going on?
I don't know the deer.
There wasn't scorpion, okay?
I mean, it was, but he was
possessed by whatever.
I jacked that kind of thing, okay?
Look, please, can I just blow up?
Slow down.
Listen, I don't know what this is,
but I need you to blow it together.
You almost killed the cop.
This isn't you.
I know, I'm sorry.
If you act like this again,
I cannot protect you.
Whatever this is, you need to fix it.
It's okay.
through lettuce, chromodynamics.
We can arrange time and
space in a grid, which allows
us to simulate the quarks
binding into the protons.
Cindy, is this a question about
protons or more stuff about Avengers?
Okay.
Guys, I love to tell
stories, but you know,
I gotta teach you some
physics at some point.
Yeah.
All right, let it rip, Cindy.
If Thanos was so worried
about overpopulation, why
didn't you just use the magic
glove to make more food?
Arthur, do you want to
answer that question?
Hulk!
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, Dr.
Banner?
I am.
You OK?
Yeah, sorry.
It's just the headache.
Um, if you got a minute, I wanted
to talk to you about your inhibitor.
Oh, sure.
Don't worry.
It's got fails, say, if
something not going to turn into
the big green-raging monster
machine in the cafeteria.
But if you do seem
to let this thing off, run.
No.
No, but you're using target-specific
short and appearing RNA, right?
It's like gene silencing.
You're just incorporating
the gamma radiation.
Would you say your name was?
Ned.
Leads.
So you found a way to suppress
the expression of DNA even as
it's undergoing the mutation
due to gamma radiation, right?
Yes.
OK.
So my question is, would
that same thing be possible
with DNA that's mutating
for another reason?
What's a reason?
I don't know.
Let's say that the host genome is
mixed with some kind of foreign DNA.
Theoretically.
Theoretically?
Yes, that's possible.
Yes.
So could you suppress only
some parts of the DNA expression?
Like the bad aspects, but
just keep all the good stuff?
You mean, like, if I wanted to
keep some parts of hot bananas?
Right.
It would be enormously
dangerous and complex, but...
If you were able to target the
correct mRNA strand, possibly.
Wait, so you could just turn
the mutating gene on and
off as long as you do it
before the mRNA transcription?
Maybe.
I mean, if you apply the same thinking,
you could even develop some kind
of automatic inhibitor that would
just adjust to any type of mutation.
Well, now you're talking
about a universal inhibitor
that would control anyone
who has any powers.
It's a dangerous idea.
Oh yeah, but it's theoretical, right?
You're not one of my students, are you?
No, I'm a grad student.
I've taken enough of your time.
I got to get some
books back to the library.
The library's that way.
Right, right.
How would you decide?
What's that?
All the parts of nature were good or bad.
What if you're trying to
control the expression
of something that
needs to be expressed?
Good luck with your studies, Ned.
Thank you, Professor.
Like reptiles and librarians
and animals, spiders
shed skin in the key
points of their life.
The process is noted.
Fourth inhibitor prototype complete
Upload inhibitor beta bill seven Uploaded.
Would you like to run a test?
Yeah, run it Spiders
have three states in their
lifecycle Each stage is
characterized by physical changes
Can you turn that spider stuff off?
Keep it on my vitals.
Inhibitor, engaged.
suppressing arachnid
hormones to your baseline levels.
Alright Evie, let's do this.
Initiating field test one.
That's working.
Alert, inhibitor is overheating.
Functionality reducing.
Yeah.
I'm sensing that.
Alert.
Stenses are overloaded.
Alert, no sense, sense,
sense, sense, sense, sense.
Alert, no sense, no sense.
Web grenades activated.
inhibitor field test one failure.
Oh, Spider-Man.
You OK?
Yeah.
I'm just trying out a new tech.
Oh, yeah.
To get rid of that monster inside you?
Still can't sense me, huh?
It should technology isn't working.
You know, you're the only
person I meant that I can't
I'm sure that's for
the frustrating for you.
Well, I'll get in there one day.
What do you want?
I don't know why a half-human have
spider would decide to work for an
organization whose one mission is
to hunt down anybody who's different.
The average control isn't after
you because you're different.
They're hunting you down
because you're dangerous.
Now, what do you want?
Since you're a very simple
spider, let me spell it out for you.
Damage control has something that I need.
Oh, you mean V-Max?
I was planning to use Scorpion to
get it, but you keep getting in my way.
I will always be in your way.
Oh, is she about that?
Peter Parker?
You know, your apartment
is kind of like a parody
where you think a sad
single guy was 20's might live.
Take our containers.
Free weights.
Protein powder?
You're bluffing.
You don't know how to track down, Peter?
Well, obese.
Not for someone like me.
I did find one interesting thing, though.
And of all places, coffee cup.
Evie, display homework station.
You spent four years of racing
Peter Parker from existence?
No wonder the spot is
trying to swallow up the man.
I wonder if MJ would even recognize you.
I think I might go see how she's doing.
I'm not going to let that happen.
No.
Her roommate was nice enough
to post a new address online.
How about this?
I'll raise you there.
If you touch her, let her start swinging.
I'm fast.
Hey, it's along with MJ's.
You better pick up the pace.
Evie, track physical anomalies.
Searching for physical anomalies
between subjects, please stand by.
Thank you all so much for coming today.
I'm sorry about that.
Give it up for Spider-Man.
In a race for the love of his
life and it's not looking good.
Come on, Spidey.
Keep up.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Evie, run these numbers with the others.
Analyzing jump distances for patterns.
Calculating.
Calculations complete.
You have a limit to your
jump radius, don't you?
33 feet.
I don't see anybody up
here for you to hop into.
Very clever.
Like I said, you're not getting near her.
Sorry, but you're in danger.
Where's your roommate?
What?
Where is there?
I lost it with friends.
Why?
Okay, good.
You gotta come with me.
What?
I don't know if you're the real spiderman.
We're coming with you.
We don't have time for this, please.
Come on.
You need to get out of my apartment.
But this is going to
sound insane, but there is
someone who is after you
who is really dangerous, okay?
And I promised you that
I would keep you safe.
Please, you just have to trust me.
Come on.
Fine.
When you stop.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay.
I wish you'd be safe up here.
Okay, we'll see from what?
Uh, I'm not entirely sure.
Okay, what do they want with me?
I don't know.
You don't know.
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would they choose me?
Um, I wish I could tell you.
I just...
Uh... We knew each other, didn't we?
What?
It's the only explanation.
It's been driving me
crazy for years all the
times that Spider-Man
saved other meat or Ned.
It was the Washington Monument and then it
was London and Prague and the Night Monkey.
I mean, twice as a coincidence,
but over and over again.
We know each other.
Tell me I'm wrong.
Well, you're wrong.
Well, where are we?
Were we classmates or friends or something?
Look, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Are we something more?
I can't.
I can't remember and I
feel like someone scrambled
my brain and you're the only
one who would know why.
This is crazy.
I know that you can't tell me the truth.
But I need to know.
Maybe there's a part of
me as to our members.
you
I think so much.
I can't believe you figured it out.
I did.
Go ahead, Peter.
Touch her.
Hold her.
You've been wanting to for so long.
True love kiss breaks the spell
and reunites the star of crosswalkers.
I'm Jacob Vaughn.
You really are a simple spider, aren't you?
I see why you like her.
She's a...
She's smart.
Funny.
A little dark and twisted.
I mean, it is sad.
There is, like, no thoughts
of you in here whatsoever.
But you knew that, didn't you?
You're a monster.
If you loved someone the
way that I love her, then you'd
know that what you're doing
right now is unforgivable.
Oh, is that so?
You know, some people would kill to
hold the person they loved one last time.
Stop it now.
Move.
You're running out of time, Peter.
Soon enough, it won't just be your
friends who don't remember Peter Parker.
Maybe you should
write a letter to yourself.
Get out of her.
Who's the monster now, Peter?
No, no, no.
Oh God.
Oh God, please, no, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, you're okay.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Stop.
Wait, stop, stop, please.
I'll quit.
You win.
Just don't hurt her.
You're a mess, Spiderman.
I need to try my wand.
I can be any one I want.
So you can't protect MJ.
Even from herself.
It really is a nice letter.
Little heavy-handed.
I'm not bad.
You're okay.
I mean, I think you're so abusive.
Take me to 3-1-6-5.
Laugh I had Street.
Navigating to Empire State University.
You're not slipping.
You're okay, you're okay,
you're okay, you're okay,
you're fine, you're fine.
You were just so down for like two seconds.
We were almost there.
Yeah, yeah, but you just
told me I was mind-control.
Well, not tell me.
Hey, you're lucky.
I believe in that stuff, OK?
Because governments have been
doing it for years, especially the French.
Are you OK?
Yeah, look, sorry.
I'm just trying to take
you someplace safe, OK?
Look.
I'm going to go see.
You're losing a kid.
Don't you be able to see
that coming a mile away.
What is wrong with you?
You could have killed us.
Here's me.
You show up to my house, son, and
now it's what he thinks is going to happen.
Wait, this is your house?
Don't go.
What the hell is that?
Who the hell are you?
She's, um, uh...
You know?
No, I don't know.
It's why I just asked you.
She's in danger, Frank.
Look, I need your help, okay?
Yeah, it looks like it.
Well, come on.
You owe me.
Ah, fuck.
What's your secretest story?
That night with that Staten Island.
What more do you want me to do?
I literally saved your life.
You're out of your mind.
What are you going to
save it twice to get a favor?
You're not going to hit
me with a handful of rights.
What does that sound like to you?
I have to be happy to shoot a guy.
I want him to do that.
I see you right there.
I don't know exactly what I'm taking.
I'll get you back in the morning.
Okay, fine.
Go ahead.
What does that sound like to you?
I don't care.
I just want to go home.
That's an excellent idea.
Kick rocks, go home.
No, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Please.
Hey, I've got to keep her safe, OK?
And I don't have anywhere else to go.
You like chili?
I made chili.
All right.
Just watch out for the clay mowers.
I won't pick up pieces at
you for the next two weeks.
Hey, I definitely would not eat that chili.
So you told me that maniac
behind all that take nonsense?
There's nothing but a goddamn teenager.
And it's not just a tank, it's every
attack on damage control this past month.
How does a kid learn how to drive a tank?
I don't know, Frank.
Be sure I saw a street like that.
She did not beat my ass.
This your family?
Check it the other way from that.
Look, I got one rule in this house.
You don't touch anything.
You don't move anything.
You sure shit don't ask many
goddamn questions about anything.
Two or three rolls.
Hmm.
That's your way you like her.
I'm gonna put some pants on.
Don't touch the jelly.
I like him.
Of course he does.
So I managed to pull those image
from my HUD and run it into the system.
Who is she?
Until a couple months ago?
Nobody.
She was in and out of foster
care, psych hospitals, and
then eventually she ran
away and dropped off the grid.
It's hardly any information about
her that hasn't been scrubbed,
but she's classified as a
telepath, and now we have a name.
Jane Gray.
Yeah.
These are the damage control
sites that she hasn't hit yet.
So, if she surfaces them, my facial
tracking program will pick her up.
Alright.
Oh yeah, what then?
Don't worry about what then.
Just look after her.
Don't worry about it, huh?
I'm just supposed to sit
here babysit your girlfriend.
I don't want to sit here
babysit your girlfriend.
All right.
Look, what's the plan, huh?
She's going to hope that your
facial tracking program works.
You get yourself killed.
I've got to watch her the rest of my life.
I'm not going to get killed, Frank.
I can catch her, OK?
I just, I just have to fix my
inhibitor and then I'll be good to go.
What do you need to do that?
Frank, you do not have
what I need to do that, OK?
I've got some mouth on you.
What do you think you
have an anti-static matte?
A tonal probe and micro tools?
I got all that shit.
What form?
Bumps.
Bingo.
Undo-leavable.
Hey, do you think it's safe to maybe
call someone and let them know I'm okay?
Uh, like your boyfriend?
No, like my roommate.
Oh.
Um, I don't think that's such a
good idea, you know, because she
already knows who he is and
she can inhabit anyone she wants.
Right.
Yeah.
You're right.
Sorry.
No, it's fine.
I totally get it.
If I call my boyfriend,
you just ask me a
bunch of questions that
I can answer and, um,
He'd tell me I was being withholding again.
With holding.
Yep.
Sounds like your
boyfriend's kind of a jerk.
Well, why do you think you're withholding?
I don't know.
He'd tell me, mass
vigilante, behind the curtain.
Okay, I see your point.
So what about you?
What about me?
Well, do you have Mrs. Spider-Man?
Do I have a Mrs. Sweater in?
No.
Why not?
Because I'm...
I'm too withholding, obviously.
Welcome to the club.
There was someone.
Really?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What happened?
I, uh...
I had to let her go.
It's like keep her safe.
I'm sorry that must've
been really hard for you.
Yeah, it was, yeah.
It is.
It is really hard.
Oh!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm okay.
It's gonna come over.
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold
on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
What's going on?
Um, it just keeps overheating on me.
It's been stumping me for days.
Before I switched to aerospace,
I was gonna major in biochemical
engineering, so... Do you
mind if I... Oh, yeah, for sure.
Here.
There you go.
Wow.
So does the device itself generate
any kind of radiation or a magnetic field?
Because that would definitely interfere.
Oh, yeah, it has a micro magnetic field,
but I accounted for that in the design.
OK, well, what about your suit?
Oh, it actually dissipates into
the fabric, which is pretty cool.
OK. What about those?
What about what?
Your goggles are very calm.
Uh, they would create a field.
It would be tiny, but...
But it's on your head, which
is very close to the inhibitor.
Which is probably why it's overheating.
Oh, MJ, that is genius.
Okay, this has to work.
Inhibitor engaged.
Surpressing selected arachnid hormones.
Okay, that feels better.
That feels totally better.
Oh, my head feels so clear.
And I'm not shooting organic webs.
Oh my God, MJ, that like totally worked.
You know, this is some really
intense stuff you're working on here.
Well, yeah, it's really important.
Yeah, but this is like, I mean,
this is like altering your DNA.
I mean, this is the kind of stuff you put
on, like, I don't know, like, a monster?
Well, if you've seen this
been happening to me over
the last couple days,
then you might understand.
Yeah, well, I've been with you for the last
few hours, and that's not what I've seen.
And what have you seen?
From my side to the curtain?
A really good guy who
might just be changing.
I don't mean to accept
all, uh, let you get back to it.
Can't sleep either, huh?
You want coffee?
Sure.
You get your shit fixed.
Yeah, I haven't been wearing it all night.
So far so good.
I made this other one universal.
So if I could get it on, Gene, it should
completely shut down her powers.
Hmm.
Yeah, what else would work?
You just shoot her.
Nice.
He's a disgrace.
That has got to be the go for
your shit I've ever seen in my life.
Well, you can't even take the mask off.
I'll drink a couple coffee.
Don't take it personally, Frank.
It stays on for everybody.
And even her.
Who is she, kid?
I don't know.
Ah, it's horseshit.
Who is she?
I'm telling you.
I don't know who she is.
I don't care about it.
Look, I don't know who she is, Frank.
OK?
I don't have anybody.
I'm like you.
I just keep to myself.
You're like me.
What do you know about me, kid?
You think this is a choice?
Living like this is a lifestyle.
Is that what you think?
Okay, this is a sentence.
You know, so if I had one second,
people I love were still breathing.
You think I'd be hiding behind a mask?
You think I'd pretend to
be something that I'm not?
Act them like a goddamn coward?
I got a facial match.
She's at the damage
control HQ in Manhattan.
I got to go.
She's going to be OK.
I'll see you to it.
Thanks, Frank.
Hey.
She's going to let him go, myself?
You know, I think he might need you.
Yeah.
Kind of like you needed
him on Staten Island.
You can't hide from me forever, Bill.
You've got a strong door, but it's
the wall you have to worry about.
Who are you and what do you want?
I'm Jeannie Gray.
And you know what I want.
Gene?
You looked me up.
I'm blushing.
I told you what would happen
to your girl if you got in my way.
You're not getting near her again.
And you're definitely not
getting inside that vault.
Maybe not.
But this guy, mate.
Gene, you don't know
what you're dealing with.
You know, you and Banner
have a lot in common.
Both fighting the losing battle
against the monster lives inside you.
Gene, this is the Hulk you can't afford!
What the hell?
Oh, I see.
Trying to muzzle me like a muzzle yourself.
I can't let you in there.
Whatever V-Max is, you're not getting it.
Like hell, I'm not.
Don't do this.
Save it, bro.
Frank, what are you doing here?
Think I'm doing I'm saving your ass.
This is way above your paper.
You can't find the whole culture.
Really?
Get out of here!
I'm shooting him!
Why are you gunting him?
He's better not the problem!
She is!
I thought I told you to
stay home and watch MJ.
Yeah, you did.
And then she tells me I
got to come watch you.
Wait does she actually say that to you?
Are you blushing?
That's a deal.
Blushing?
Goddamn it.
I knew I should have bought a bigger gun.
That's a good idea.
Bring a bigger girl.
What are you gonna do?
Take her in the death?
No, look.
Change your planet.
First we get this on the Hulk.
Then we go after G. I got one better.
That's the highest
casualty bruce in threat.
You contain it.
I go find the source.
I take it down.
You got it?
Are you just trying to get
out of fighting the Hulk?
I guess so.
Okay, whatever, dude.
I got this.
I don't think I could.
What?
Do not kill her.
Don't start with that soft serve bullshit.
Don't stop.
I'm gonna do this.
I'm gonna do my way.
Just go.
Don't get within 33 feet.
Yeah.
So frustrating.
Hey.
Whoa.
This guy's got issues.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, again.
Talk to better.
Is that you?
Hey, hey, hey.
Did I do all this?
Yeah.
Did I hurt anyone?
It's not your fault.
She was in your mind.
You weren't in control.
I lost my own heaven.
Look, here, here.
It's the only thing keeping
the monster inside.
It's OK.
I got another one.
I just need you to put this on.
What is it?
It's universal.
It should work on you.
Please start.
There's people in the building.
Just put it on.
You okay?
It's my head.
I think she broke something.
Is she still in there?
No.
It's the other guy.
Bruce?
Look, I could get you out of here, okay?
He just need you to put that inhibitor on.
You're right for me!
He's coming.
I can't get you.
Yes, you can, Bruce.
Yes, you can!
Get out of the building!
No!
Better, please!
Look at me!
No, Ben!
No, girl!
Follow me all!
I didn't know you could get that big.
Wow.
Good luck with that, Peter.
No leave for around.
Tracking time to detonation.
90 seconds to detonation.
I know that!
I know!
Why is your skin so thick?
Inhibitors cannot attack.
No!
Come on!
Look at that.
Please.
Bruce.
It's Peter.
I'll be your friend.
Throughout on your guns, I'll
get the next one in the head.
Where is she?
It's over Jean.
Sarah?
Is that my gun?
Is anyone hurt?
Is it just me?
Is that one hurt?
Spider-Man.
You saved my life.
And you saved God knows
how many lives by making sure
she didn't find what she
was looking for in there.
Before she passed out,
she tried to say something.
A name, Sarah.
Does that mean something to you?
Before you got the inhibitor on her, she
managed to get in my mind for a moment.
Sarah was the name of someone I
worked closely with every silly past.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Somehow the memory of
Sarah must have affected her.
Well, I'd love to talk to
her when she wakes up.
That's all right.
But of course, she'll be transferred
to our facility on Roosevelt Island.
Now, I'm just as eager to
get her talking as you are.
But let's not strain her
too much in one day.
Yeah, of course.
Thank you, Spider-Man.
My pleasure.
But Jay, the work she's in custody.
You're safe now.
You left this?
Did you want me to find it?
No.
Um, look, I can explain.
I need to take that off, please.
What?
The mask.
I think I deserve to have this
conversation with Peter Parker.
He came to the party at
our apartment the other night.
And the donut shop.
The year I went off to school.
Why didn't you tell me then?
I was trying to protect you.
I've almost been killed
like five times the past
24 hours, so it's not
really working that well.
I know I'm sorry.
Were you ever gonna tell me?
Right.
So you just were gonna
make that decision for me?
I know, I'm sorry.
I don't really need you to
keep saying that you're sorry.
I don't know what you want me to tell me.
I want you to tell me why
you would do this to me.
I lost someone.
And I'd still be here if it wasn't for me.
I didn't read you that
letter because I didn't
want anything like
that to happen to you.
That's not really your decision.
I know it's not, but you
mean everything to me.
And I've been trying to live
my life without you, but I can't.
this spell or whatever it is that you did.
It worked.
All these memories that you're saying
that we have together, I don't have them.
And I do see why, you
know, she would love you.
The girl you wrote that letter to, but
I understand that you did what
you had to do to protect her.
And for that, I'm so grateful.
But I...
I don't love you.
You said I don't... I
don't even know you.
I should probably go now.
I really am sorry, but here.
Do you mind taking me home?
Yeah, of course.
Thank you.
Yeah, sure.
Um, I'm gonna, uh... Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Do you wanna come up?
Just to say hi to Ned, maybe?
I would love that.
The Hulk, AKA Dr. Bruce
Banner, is in custody currently being
transferred to a psychiatric ward
after years as a peaceful academic.
The question the world asked
today is, what finally snapped?
Hey, I'm nearby.
Indeed?
Yeah.
Hey, I'm nearby.
Hi.
You're not gonna believe this.
But the Spidey Tracker app says
that Spider-Man is in the direct vicinity.
Oh yeah?
No way, that's crazy.
Uh, Ned, Spider-Man, Spider-Man, Ned?
It's nice to meet you, Ned.
Hello.
I'm not like a weird old for anything.
He's a little weird.
Why?
Why are you here?
Oh, I was on the subway platform, right?
And she was on her phone.
I got a little distracted
and the train was coming.
And I just swooped it right up.
Save it now.
Oh, my God.
Why does that never happen to me?
So what if you're mid-swing
and you decide you need a P?
Do you just land on top of a building?
What?
Do you drop down the ground level
and run into a coffee shop and you're
like, hey, it's Spider-Man, I need a P.
Or do you find a rooftop somewhere?
No, I don't find a rooftop somewhere, Ned.
Is this really what you want
to be asking him right now?
Yeah, dude, come on.
You can ask me anything.
You want to know how my web shooters work?
I mean, I already know
how the web shooters work.
Is that right?
Well, there's obviously
some sort of sheer thinning
fluid that is cycling
within a chamber, right?
So we can keep a slipwood form.
And then when you activate it by
pressing all the triggers, it runs through
a Teflon turbine, and then it hardens
when it interacts with the air, right?
I mean, not exactly, but...
Okay, okay.
Well, then tell me what's in the web fluid.
I would guess something like
a long-shane polymer nylon.
That's pretty close.
Okay, okay.
What about no-max or... Oh, Kevlar?
All right, then keep your secrets.
If you're very good at the edges
with the dragon, I was barely involved.
All I did was simply give your
uncle a little nudge out the door.
Solid reference.
Oh, bond me time.
You ordered bond me.
I ordered five bond me's.
We have Spider-Man in the apartment.
He's going to get found.
Sorry about him.
He's just like very
excited that you're here.
Are you kidding?
It's like the most fun I've had in years.
I really missed you guys.
You guys really do look like best friends.
What do you mean?
You should tell him.
You can handle it.
Yeah, I know.
When she was inhabiting you
on the rooftop, she kissed me and I
kissed her back because I
thought it was you, but I didn't know.
And I'm really sorry.
I just thought you should know.
Thanks for telling me.
I mean, it's not like I
remember anything anyway, so.
Really?
Yeah.
It was weird.
It was like one second.
I was sitting at my
desk in the next second.
I was lying on the street.
I remember like a light switch went off.
What?
So you don't remember anything?
No way.
That's Chris said he remembered
thinking about someone named Sarah,
but what you're saying is that
you don't remember anything at all.
I mean, yeah, it was instantaneous.
That's what made it so scary.
He lied to me.
I heard you caught fleshy.
Yeah, my name's Jean Grey.
I need some help determining
the size of some potatoes.
I think Metzka lied to me about a name.
Can you see if there's a connection
between Jean and someone named Sarah?
Hmm, this potato sound meager.
Oh, well, that really is your office.
Well, well, well.
Internet, government records,
and a lot of data related
to Jean Grey has been
scrubbed by damage control.
They're about what?
Her sister.
Wait, Jean has a sister.
Hmm, Sarah Grey.
Also a telepath, damage
control took her into custody.
For study and observation.
Wow.
And then you can probably
guess what they meant by that.
It's a experimentation in
other human rights violations.
Yes, exactly.
Wait, who are you?
Hi.
That leads.
Pick that.
Hi.
I'm sorry.
I'm just so happy that
this admin has friends.
Uh-huh.
Thanks.
I owe you one.
Good luck, Spider-Man.
She was just looking for her sister, and
I handed her to the people that took her.
I gotta go.
Get Peter?
Just be here, Faray.
Yeah, I love you.
Spider-Man's name is Peter.
Gene, who do you want to be?
Her pink jacket.
She's too far.
You get up to hop.
First, pick someone close.
And then...
Each hop has a limit, but you can string
them together and go as far as you want.
And when you let go,
you're up after you started.
Could you do that to
everyone in this park at once?
Yeah, maybe one day if you get really good.
Now could she just... send us away.
She wasn't really a mom.
Not like that anyway.
She was.
Before we changed.
Yeah, well, that's all it takes for you to
stop being a mom that you're not a mom.
What would you do if
you had daughters like us?
I'd love them.
Especially the redhead.
Shut up.
We have each other.
Can we have ice cream?
One mint chip one chocolate?
Yeah.
I'm sorry Gene.
I have to keep you safe.
Subject is awake, heart rate is 94 BPM.
Jane, that's not gonna work anymore.
Thanks to Spider-Man.
I need you to breathe.
I need you to look at me and breathe.
Okay?
You're safe.
Breathe.
Where is she?
Like your sister, you've been
blessed with a power that has the
potential to do tremendous good
in the world or tremendous damage.
A power like yours in the hands
of a child is an impossible burden.
But imagine.
If that power was placed in the hands of
people who actually know what to do with it.
Where is my sister?
You're going to change the world, Jane.
Right?
And know where you are, what you're doing.
Oh, yeah, and how's that?
You got eyes everywhere, kid.
Look, Frank, damage
control, kidnapped Gene Sister.
Gene was just trying to find her.
We were wrong about everything.
Sedimental horse shit.
You see him when she can do what she's capable
of, what you're going to let her loose.
Is that what you're going to do?
Tell you right now, you do that.
I handle it my way.
Frank, please be here today.
Frank!
Distance check.
40-foot clearance.
Lock him down the room.
Lock him down.
Disengage inhibitor.
Jane, your power's
enough fully operational.
As you can tell, we're
beyond your jump radius.
Tell me what Vie Max is.
The other second person
to ask me about that.
I have no idea what that means.
She sent me a message.
She was trying to help me find her.
She communicated with you
telepathically across all that distance.
We did register a huge
spike in that session.
Fascinated.
What does it mean, asshole?
I don't know.
Let's begin.
Our work with Sarah centered on two areas.
Identifying the source of her power
and identifying a path towards copying it.
If we could find a way to record a
telepathic brain during a jump, then
perhaps we could replicate those
pathways in a mind of our choosing.
This instrument is your sister's legacy.
We built this together over
many months of trial and error.
I hope you and I can honor his sacrifice.
What are you talking about?
Trigger the first jump.
Tell me what V-Max is.
I know that's where you're hiding her.
She's jumping.
Copy.
We're in full lockdown.
Process has commenced.
What process?
Hey, whoa, that's a pretty
serious look there, dude.
Hey, hey, whoa, what the hell, man?
Come on, I'm a friend of damage control.
What are you doing?
Huh, it's going to be like that.
You want to go.
All right.
Just give me a sec.
Give me a sec.
I'm not in high school anymore.
Oh.
Did you stretch your big structure?
I mean, you should do
and your line of work.
What about you?
You guys stretch?
It's so good for you.
You ready?
Where is Jean Grey?
Let's jump 26.
Recordings look good.
Excuse me, sir.
We have an intruder.
You were right.
She's much stronger than a sister.
Increase the frequency.
Jane?
Jane, can you hear me?
You're a murderer.
A frequency's are evolving.
This doesn't make sense.
The last thing my sister saw was this room.
The brain waves are somehow
affecting the objects around her.
Shut it down.
I'm trying, sir.
What do you mean you're trying?
The last thing my sister
saw was this goddamn lab!
Shut it down!
I can't, sir.
Move.
I can't let you do that, Bill.
The only hands that will
wield this power are mine.
No!
What do you want?
Jean, I'm here to help you.
You put me here.
I know, and I'm sorry about Sarah,
and I'm sorry that I got it so wrong.
If you came here to save a helpless
girl from damage control, you're too late.
They're the ones who need saving.
And now, so do you.
What?
Isn't it funny how your
friends from damage
control developed a
special weapon just for you?
They've got a whole task force ready.
Just in case you ever get out of line.
People are monsters.
You shouldn't trust them
any more than they trust you.
My little busy, Frank.
You've got a bum, kid.
You've got to hold everyone
within a kilometer in the island.
Wait, what?
Look, if you're gonna do
something, you better do it now!
I'm trying!
Get it!
Oh my god!
My sister died in this room
surrounded by these men.
And her only crime was that she
was special, just like you, just like me.
People like us don't
get to live a normal life.
We don't get to have friends or a family.
Those people are gone.
That life is over.
So why don't you just
be honest with yourself?
Are you Peter Parker?
Or are you Spider-Man?
on both.
Oh!
Jean, please.
This won't make it right.
Come on, you're not a killer, Gene.
You have no idea what I am.
I know that you loved your sister.
And I know that losing her
felt like he'd lost everything.
If you come any closer, he dies.
They all do.
You know, this won't
bring her back, right, Jesus?
Don't be so sure I kick it into your mind.
I'm a lot more powerful since I last tried.
I think you don't have to
listen to me and I've got palace.
You know, this whole
thing would get really scary.
You know that?
It's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And these can change very quickly
ways that we can't even imagine right now.
I know.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
You're a really special person.
And I would hope that that will always
make you feel really great about yourself.
But I know sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes it'll be really lonely.
And sometimes because you're special,
people can do dark, monstrous things to you.
But this is what I want you to know.
You're beautiful.
And the people who love you, we love you.
Not because you're special,
we love you because you're you.
I want you to remember that.
Even when it feels
like you're totally alone.
That's your deepest responsibility.
Never forget that no
matter how powerful you
I'm sorry about your sister.
I'm sorry about your aunt.
Yeah, you would've loved her.
Just because we've lost someone.
It doesn't mean we have to do this alone.
I mean...
We can't trust me I've been trying.
It doesn't work.
Even if that's true.
I have no one.
You heard?
Fine.
I'm okay.
Peter.
Peter!
No, no, no, no.
You gotta get out of here.
Don't be looking for you.
No, no, no, no, no.
Please just stay with me.
Come on, hold on.
Come on, please!
Just go.
Get up.
Look at me.
Shocked today, a
Spider-Man arrived to Bellevue
Hospital with a bullet wound,
seemingly at that store.
The reclusive crime fighter
has in critical condition
as the city's top medical
experts work to save him.
Tonight, all eyes are on Spider-Man.
The hero who saved
New York so many times is
now in the hands of
its best and brightest.
And the people of New
York hold their breath.
Where am I?
No, no, no, no, no.
Where's my mask?
You're good.
Where's Jean is she okay?
Yeah, she's okay.
She's okay.
Where is she?
They maybe she just left.
She was using her magic
voodoo shit to keep you alive.
Yeah, she's all right.
I'm sorry.
I can't suggest you some.
I'm really sorry for what I did.
No, thank you.
You know, it's a lot of things,
but it sure is shitting, OK?
All right.
I see him.
I see real bravery kid my day.
But that was something else.
You crying?
No.
I ain't good.
No, you looked exactly
where I thought you would.
You're a nice kid.
Never had a friend like that.
And we friends now.
I can't believe I just saw you cry.
I was probably talking about, oh shit.
Oh, yeah.
They've been doing it all night.
Been here since you walked in.
Just take a look.
You okay?
You came in there to cut through
the soup, but when you're ready to split,
I got a plan.
Hey!
It's Spider-Man!
Yeah!
Come on, come on!
.
I've, uh...
I'm thinking a lot about what you said.
And you'd be happy to know
that I've decided I'm not...
I'm not gonna do this alone anymore.
Let me see me.
I mean, I've stuck a little
pain in my back, but I could
probably get back out there
if you need me for anything.
What I need you to do is rest.
I know, I know, but come on,
you gotta give me something.
I mean, how's the investigation going?
Well, let's go to stone this scene.
But your friend, Black Widow,
she's been helping us dig through
all the records, damage
control, tried to have scrubbed.
Have me drop my office together there?
And how is that?
Well, uh, my skin feels amazing.
Attention all units.
We have a confirmed
bank robbery in progress.
Hey, you getting this?
Yeah, I'm on it.
Hey, it's not that far from me.
I could probably meet you down there.
No, we can handle a robbery.
Just try to take care of yourself.
OK. You too.
Say hello to E.J.
Marley for me.
OK. Spider-Man says hello?
I'm going to go.
Uh, hey.
Oh, whoa, uh, flower guy, right?
From the party?
I'm Peter.
Okay, hello.
Come on, come on, come on
I don't wanna lose again
these I've made from my whole
you.
you
I'm sorry.
you you
No spiderman sighting.
Location?
A no.
Location, location, unknown.
Location, unknown.
Location, found.